打开SunShine这个App，我们创建一个
Open up the Sunshine app. And we'll create a
新的文件夹给我们的ForecastAdapter，扩展的游标适配器。我们
new file for our ForecastAdapter, which extends CursorAdapter. We
提供了一个代码的列表来开始
provided you with a gist of code to get started
下面的部分。这些代码重载了newView类函数，实例化了
below. The code overrides the newView method, where it inflates
list_item_forecast的布局分布XML。它同时提供了
the list_item_forecast layout XML. It also provides
bindView函数的实现，从游标读取数据
an implementation for bindView, where it reads from the cursor,
更新布局。举个例子，从游标看，我们
and updates the layout. For example, from the cursor, we
读取了天气预报的描述，然后我们到
read the weather forecast description. Then we go and find
TextView     在列表的视图层次结构里
the TextView for that within the view hierarchy of the
我们寻找了TextView 通过ID
list item layout. We look for the TextView  with the id
list_item_forecast_textview。然后我们更新
list_item_forecast_textview. Then we update the
TextView用正确的描述。我们
textview with the right description. We
也在代码里留下一些to do。所以，继续，
also left some to dos in the code. So, go ahead and
复制文件的内容，完成这些to do。
copy over the file and then finish the to dos. In
现有的实现中，所有的日期都是同样方式显示的。
the current implementation of the app, all dates are displayed the same.
尽管是在线框里，你会发现我们有一个更为友好的
In the wireframes though, you'll notice that we have a more friendly
日期格式。在要点中我们也包含了一些辅助函数还有
date format. In the gist we also included some helper methods and
日期格式化的字符串。这是由于在我们现有的
strings for date formatting. That's because in our current
实现中，所有的日期都用相同的方式显示。
implementation, all the dates are displayed in the same way.
尽管是在线框里，我们有一个更为友好的日期
In the wireframes though, we have a more friendly date
类型，比如今天，明天，周三，周四等等。这是
format. Such as today, tomorrow, Wednesday, Thursday, etc. Here's that
辅助方法的逻辑可以达到的
logic for what the helper method does to get the
用户友好的字符串。如果是在这周，会显示今天
friendly date string. If it's this week it says today,
或者明天，或者这周的某一天。如果是
or tomorrow, or the day of the week. If it's
一周以外，我们将会使用这样的格式：
more than a week out then we use the format
周一，六月八日，等等。当你完成这些
Monday, June 8th and so on. Once you finish the
to do并添加了辅助方法和字符串，
to dos and you added the helper methods and strings,
然后继续换掉简单的游标适配器，利用
then go ahead and replace the simple CursorAdapter with
ForecastAdapter。当你完成并运行这个app，它会
a ForecastAdapter. After you compile and run the app it'll
看上去和之前一样，唯独有一个列表的项目
look the same as before with only one list item
视图类型类型显示出来，尽管现在正在用的ForecastAdapter。
view type shown, except now it's using a ForecastAdapter and
现在有更好的日期描述。我记得我
now it has better date descriptions. I know that I
承诺过你们游标适配器可以处理多重项目视图类型
promised you that CursorAdapter could handle multiple item view types,
所以我们将会在下一步继续进行。
so we'll do that in the next step.